(Leonard:)What do we do...
kick them off?
(Penny:)If we drop them off
at a fire station,
they have to take them;
no questions asked.
(Sheldon:)Before you do, please
give me one more chance
(Sheldon:)to apologize to Emily.
(Raj:)Oh, God.
(Sheldon:)Emily, as I'm
sure you know,
(Sheldon:)I'm considered
an odd fellow.
(Sheldon:)But what you don't know
is that, while I often
(Sheldon:)say the wrong thing,
in my heart I mean well.
(Sheldon:)I think that you are
(Sheldon:)a smart and wonderful
woman, you know?
(Sheldon:)And we all think that you can
do better than Koothrappali.
(Raj:)You know, Sheldon...
(Emily:)Shh, let him finish.
(Sheldon:)So, for all the times
I've offended you
(Sheldon:)and all the times that
I'll offend you in the future,
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Leonard:)Good.
(Sheldon:)Then I'll be leaving now.
(Emily:)Oh, it's okay, Sheldon.
(Emily:)Come with us.
(Sheldon:)Oh, that's very kind of you.
(Sheldon:)But I'm sure you'll all have
a better time without me.
(Sheldon:)Let's go, Stuart.
(Stuart:)But I want to stay.
Stuart, now!
(Sheldon:)You know,
I know he's a jerk,
(Emily:)but I actually
feel bad for him.
(Penny:)And now you see
the problem.
Come on, you pain in the ass!
That's me!
(Sheldon:)Bye, Stuart.
Wait!
I'm a pain in the ass, too!
(Sheldon:)Are you relieved
that you and Raj
(Sheldon:)were able
to patch things up?
(Emily:)At the moment?
(Emily:)No, not really.
♪ Burn, baby, burn... ♪
Shake it, baby!
(whoops)
Work that thing!